Biophysical Society records
Biophysical Society records
- Series I. Officers and Executive Committee, 1955-2002; 11.25 linear feet
  - Subseries I.B. Correspondence, 1955-1998; 121 folders (5.25 linear feet)
    - Correspondence/Biophysical Society & Legation Press re 6th Biophysical Discussion, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence/B.S. Trust Co. Visa/MC (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence/Careers in Biophysics, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence/Charter Flight to Stockholm, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence/Cole Award, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Commission on Research Integrity, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/Congressional Educator, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/Consensus Statement on Biomedical Research Funding, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence/Data Manager (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence/Database Conference, June 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Directory, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Editorial Board, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence/Electronic Publications Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence/Executive Board, 1957-1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/Executive Director Search, May-July 1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence/Executive Director Search, August-October, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/FASEB, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence/FASEB, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/FASEB, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence/Finance Committee, 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence/Finance Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence/Finance Email 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence/Foreign Journals, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence/Government Grants, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence/Grey, E., 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/Innovative Technology Fund, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence/Kyros Associates, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence/Lecture Tour, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence/Lobbying, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence/Membrane Structure & Assembly Subgroup, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence/Memos on Office of Scientific Integrity, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence/NAS-NRC Relations, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence/Neutron Structural Biology Task Force, 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence/NIH Application for Support, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence/P.I.R., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence/Placement Service, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence/Plans for Biophysical Journal, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence/Samuel A. Talbot Memorial, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence/Setlow, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence/Snell Resolution, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence/Society Logos, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence/Subgroups, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence/Teleconference, September 7, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence/Travel Grants, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence/Triangle Coalition, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence/U.S. Gov/HHS and Education, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence/US National Committee for Pure and Applied Biophysics, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence/USNC PAB, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence/USNC PAB, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Email/Biophysical Journal Electronic Publishing, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Email/Biophysical Society Database Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Email/Biophysical Society Database Report, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Email/Electronic Publication Initiative, 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Email/Executive Director Search, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Email/Post-Presidency Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Email/Presidency, July 1995-Feb 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Email/Presidency, Feb-May 1996(1) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Email/Presidency, Feb-May 1996(2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Email/Presidency, May-Sept 1996(1) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Email/Presidency, May-Sept 1996(2) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Email/Presidency, Dec 1996-May 1997(1) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Email/Presidency, Dec 1996-May 1997(2) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Email/Presidency, Dec 1996-May 1997(3) (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Email/Secretariat, March 1994-May 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Email/Secretariat, May 1995-March 1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Email/Secretariat, April 1996-July 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Email/Secretariat, April 1996-March 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Subseries I.C. Executive Board Meetings, 1956-2002; bulk 1971-1999; 71 folders (4 linear feet)
    Agendas, Correspondence, Minutes, and Reports of the Executive Board; arranged in date order.
    - Executive Board and Council Meetings, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Executive Board and Council Meetings, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1971 (Feb) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board Meetings,1971 (April & Sept) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1972 (Feb) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1972 (April) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1972 (Sept) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1973 (Feb-March) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1973 (June & Dec) (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1974 (June 2) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1974 (Sept 14) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1975 (Feb 18) (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1975 (May 10) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1975 (Sept 20) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1989 (Feb) (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1989 (May) (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1989 (Oct) (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1990 (Feb) (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1990 April/Agenda (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1990 (April) (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1990 (Oct) (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1991 (Feb) (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1991 (May) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1991 (Oct) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Full Council Meeting, 1992 (Feb 8) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1992 (Feb) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1992 (May) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1992 (Oct) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1992 (Oct) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (Feb) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (Feb) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (May) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (May) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Executive Board Meetings, Correspondence, 1993 (May) (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (Oct) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (Oct) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Executive Board Meetings, Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1994 (March) (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1994 (March) (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1994 (May) (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1994 (May) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1994 (Oct) (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1994 (Oct) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1995 (Feb) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1995 (Feb) (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1995 (May) (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1995 (May) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1995 (Sept) (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1995 (Sept) (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1996 (Feb) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1996 (Feb) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1996 (June) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1996 (June) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1996 (Oct) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1996 (Oct) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1997 (March) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1997 (March) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1997 (June) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1997 (June) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1997 (Oct) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1997 (Oct) (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1998 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1998 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1998 (May) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1998 (May) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1998 (Sept) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1998 (Sept) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1999 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1999 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1999 (April) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1999 (Nov) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 2000 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 2001 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 2001 (May) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 2002 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Subseries I.D. Finances, 1957-1998; bulk 1974-1995; 39 folders (1.25 linear feet)
    Reports, budgets, subgroup budgets, miscellaneous financial documents arranged in alphabetical order by type of document.
    - Accounts/Dean Witter, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Accounts/Dean Witter Trust, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Accounts/Insurance, 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Accounts/Joint Steering Committee, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Accounts/Subgroups, 1974-1985 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Accounts/Subgroups, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Accounts/Subgroups, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Accounts/Subgroups, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Accounts/Trust Company, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Accounts/Union Trust Company, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Budgets/Society Budget, 1987-1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Budgets/Education Committee Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Budgets/Meetings Budgets, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Reports/Audit, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Reports/Consolidated Financial Statements, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Reports/Consolidated Financial Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Reports/Consolidated Financial Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Reports/Consolidated Financial Statements, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Reports/Consolidated Financial Statements, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Reports/Financial Statements, 1961-1971 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Reports/Financial Statements, 1988-1993 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Reports/Finance Committee, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Reports/Finance Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Reports/General Ledger, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Reports/Innovative Technology Fund, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Reports/Membership & Subscription, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Reports/Mid-year Report, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Reports/Misc. Financial, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Reports/Quarterly Financial, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Reports/Quarterly Financial, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Reports/Quarterly Financial, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Reports/Treasurer, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Reports/Treasurer, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Reports/Treasurer, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Reports/Treasurer, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Reports/Treasurer, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Taxes, 1964, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Grant Proposals, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Grants, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Subseries I.E. Administrative Files, 1956-1998; bulk 1961-1973; 16 folders (.5 linear feet)
    Officer's administrative records arranged in alphabetical order by type of document.
    - Archival Creation, 1956, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Form Letters/Secretary, 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Mailings (Secretary), 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Mailings (Secretary), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Mailings (Secretary), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Mailings (Secretary), 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Mailings (Secretary), 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Secretary/Membership, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Programs/National Labs (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Questionnaire (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Reports/Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Reports/Neutron Scattering (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Reports/President, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Reports/President, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Reports/Secretary, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Rosters, 1959-1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Series II. Meetings, 1956-2002; bulk 1963-1997; 173 folders (7.25 linear feet)
  Minutes, agendas, announcements, correspondence, programs, reports, rosters, and memos arranged into two Subseries: Annual Meetings and Miscellaneous Meetings and Conferences.
  - Subseries II.A. Annual Meetings, 1956-2000; bulk 1963-1997; 164 folders (7 linear feet)
    Correspondence, minutes, agendas, programs, abstracts, contracts, rosters, announcements, memos, and notes arranged in order by meeting date.
    - Minutes, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Program Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - First Biophysics Conference, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - National Meeting, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Meeting Information, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Announcements and Programs, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Agenda, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Meeting Information, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Materials and Minutes, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Meeting Information, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Program Committee, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Professional Associates (Contracts), 1962-1966 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Agenda, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence (Professional Associates), 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Non-members Attending List, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Old Council, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Materials and Minutes, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Meeting Information, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Scrapbook (Howard Mil-Local Arrangements Chairman)/1965 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Business Meeting, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Local Arrangements, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Meeting Announcements, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Muscle Session, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - New Council Meeting, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Old Council Meetings, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Program Committee, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Agenda, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Local Arrangements Committee, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Program Committee, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - New Council I, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - New Council II Meeting, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Non-members Attending, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Old COuncil Meetings, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Information, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Agenda, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Local Arrangements Committee, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Information, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Non-members Attending, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Program Committee, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (4/1965-2/1968), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Requests for Information), 9/1967-1/1968/1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Change of Meeting Place, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Meeting Place Information (Pittsburgh, PA.) and Agenda, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Non-members Forms, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Program Committee, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Abstract Forms and Committee Members, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Attendance Lis, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Buisness Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Change of Location, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Charter Flight Reservations, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Local Arrangements, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Requests for Meeting Information (4/1968-2/1969), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Travel Awards, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Workshops, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Attendance List, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Requests for Information, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Local Arrangements Committee, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Meeting Information and Call for Papers, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Program Committee, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Requests for Information, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Buisness Meeting, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Invitation to Attend, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - New Council Meetings II, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - New Council Meetings I, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Old Council and Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Meeting Information, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence (Hebrew), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Meeting Information, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Meeting Information & Call for Papers, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Abstract Books, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Misc. Arrangements, Guest Reimbursements, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Call for Papers, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence (4/1983-8/1985), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Exhibitors, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Minutes, Notes (Steve White), Symposia Room Assignments, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Revenue and Expenses, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Symposia Notes, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Information and Call for Papers, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Nominations, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Arrangements (Housing), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Minutes, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Minutes, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Symposia, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Program Chairman's Guide (Proposal and Suggestion Materials), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Agenda and Minutes (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence, General (1989-1990), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence, Registration, Waiver Requests (10/1989-5/31/1990), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Exhibitor, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Latin American Grants (Latin American Initiative), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Latin American Initiative/Travel Grants, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Revenue and Expenses, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Registration Statistics, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Travel, Talbot Awards, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Expenses and Statistics, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Materials, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Mailing Labels, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Travel, Talbot Awards, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Exhibitions Responses to Questionnaire, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Exhibitors, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Expenses and Reimbursement, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Latin American Initiative (Travel Grants), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Meeting Planning, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Meeting Registration, Expenses, and Materials, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Statistics and Suggestions, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Travel Awards (Students), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Exhibitors, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Expenses and Reimbursements, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Latin American and Eastern Block Initiative, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Registration Waivers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Meeting Revenue and Expenses, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Statistical Reports, Contracts and License, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Travel Awards (Students), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - 1994 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Attendees, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Expenses and Reimbursements (5/1993-3/1994), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Expenses and Reimbursements (4/1994-8/1994), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Expenses, Revenues and Statistics, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Travel Grants (Students), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Report, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Student Travel Awards, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Meeting Planning Materials/1997 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - National Lecturer (David Eisenberg)/1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Site Proposal, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Abstracts, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Abstracts, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Abstracts, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Abstracts, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Abstracts, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Abstracts, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Abstracts, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Abstracts, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Abstracts, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Abstracts, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Abstracts, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Abstracts, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Abstracts, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Abstracts, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Abstracts, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Abstracts, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Abstracts, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Abstracts, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Abstracts, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Abstracts, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Abstracts 2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Brochures (Information & Call for Papers), 1986-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Brochures (Information & Call for Papers), 1996, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Programs, 1957, 1958-1959 (with Abstracts) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Programs, 1960-1962, 1964-1965, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Programs, 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Programs, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Programs, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)